immunodx.com 2005-04-04

# Privacy

|        
**Privacy Policy:  
**This policy is subject to change at any time, check back regularly.

**ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated.   

  * **What information is collected?**
  * **What about cookies?**
  * **Who collects the information?**
  * **How is the information used?**
  * **With whom will you share the information?**
  * **What are my choices regarding my information?**
  * **What security procedures are in place to protect  
my information?**
  * **What about children's safety and privacy?**
  * **What else should I know?**

Questions regarding this policy should be directed to: **[immunodx@immunodx.com](mailto:immunodx@immunodx.com) **

**What information is collected?  
ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** may collect information in a variety of ways. Some information is gathered when you send feedback, or order from us. During that process, **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** may ask for your name, email address, and other personal information. In addition, we may obtain and retain your IP address. An IP address is generally considered non-private information.  There may be times when we ask you for personal information, including (but not limited to) when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** , or when you subscribe to various services we may provide. If you contact **I mmunoDiagnostics, Inc.**, we may keep a record of that correspondence. **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** also occasionally asks users to complete surveys that we use for research purposes. All other information gathered is optional.

****

**What about cookies?  
ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** may at some points use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you, measure the effectiveness of banner advertising and analyze site activity. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer. 

**ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** **  
** When you are on [www.immunodx.com](http://www.immunodx.com/) and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information solely with **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** , unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Please be aware that **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** advertisers or web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those web sites are not covered by this privacy statement. 

**How is the information used?  
****ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a customized service. **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** also does research on our member's demographics, interests and behavior based on the information provided to us via feedback, surveys, during a promotion, or from our server logs. The data is compiled and analyzed on a regular basis. **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** may share this demographical data with advertisers or business partners.

**With whom will you share the information?  
**As a general rule, **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** may preserve Content and may disclose Content to any third party if required to do so by law or in good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is necessary to comply with legal process or enforce the Terms of Service.

**What are my choices regarding my information?  
ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** may send you email regarding our products and services. In addition, if you indicated that you are interested in receiving offers or information from **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.,** we may occasionally send you direct mail about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive these mailings, simply follow the instructions in the email to be removed from future mailings.  By modifying your browser preferences, you can choose to accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set or to accept no cookies. If you choose to accept no cookies, you may be unable to use parts of the **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** website. **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** **** does not sell or rent user information to anyone. 

****

**What security procedures are in place to protect my information?  
**We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Remember to log off your computer or close your browser window when you have finished your work to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence. No data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, **ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

**** **What about children's safety and privacy?**  
**ImmunoDiagnostics, Inc.** is geared toward an audience of consumers. A consumer for our purposes is defined as someone who has the legal ability and right to purchase items with a credit card or check.  We will not knowingly transact business with anyone under the age of 18. ****

**What else should I know?**  
Whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, including in your email correspondence, that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you disclose personal information online that is accessible to others, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  You are ultimately and solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any information about yourself. Please be careful and responsible when you are online.

**** |
